《打工姐妹花》前情提要
Previously on 2 Broke Girls...
惨了 麦克斯 我的钱包丢了
Oh, no, Max! My wallet! It's gone.
我们所有的现金跟信用卡都在里面呢
All of our cash and our credit cards were in there.
我真的得去德州见我男朋友
I need to get to Texas to see my boyfriend.
肯定有办法能解决
There has got to be a way we can work something out.
我们什么都愿意做
We'll do anything.
又是一个在德州的孤独夜
Just another lonely night here in Texas...
跟我的一帮新朋友共度
with all my new best friends!
我正好开车去德州 你们想搭顺风车吗
I'm driving to Texas if y'all want a ride.
我要坐前排 我要坐鲁保罗旁边
Shotgun! I'm sitting next to RuPaul.
不 我要坐鲁保罗旁边
No. I'm sitting next to RuPaul!
好啦
All right.
所以这里就是兰迪跟其他电影人住的地方
So, this is where Randy and the other movie people are staying.
他曾在这里待过 我闻到腹肌的味道
He's been here. I smell abs.
我闻到了我们的臭味
Ugh, I smell us.
我什么时候吃过了热狗啊
When did I have a hot dog?
我在你睡着时跟你分吃了一根 不客气
I shared one with you while you were sleeping. You're welcome.
问问那个柜台人员有没见过兰迪
Let's ask that clerk if he's seen Randy,
以及自动浇水机几点启动 我们好洗个澡
and when the outdoor sprinklers go on so we can freshen up.
您好 有何能为您效劳
Hi. How can I help you?
对了 如果你们是故意打扮成
B-T-dubs, if you're going for that tossled,
刚从坑里爬出来的张牙舞爪样
just-crawled-out-of-a-ditch look,
简直完美
you nailed it.
我就不问你是刚从哪爬出来了
I'm not gonna ask what you just crawled out of,
我累到没力对你毒舌
because I'm too tired to be mean.
所以呢 里奇
So, Richie,
我与我同事想知道
my associate and I would like to know
兰迪·沃尔什住在哪间房
what room Randy Walsh is staying in.
我还注意到这里严格执行"禁带宠物"规定啊
And I see you have a very strict "No pets" policy.
好的 兰迪·沃尔什的房号 没问题
Yes, Randy Walsh's room. Of course.
他的房间号码好像是...
Looks like he is in room number...
世界上哪有酒店柜台会泄露住客信息
what hotel clerk in the world would give out a guest's info
给两个脏兮兮的怪咖啊
to two dusty randos?
老娘可不只是脏兮兮的怪咖
Um, I'm more than just a dusty rando.
我可是他脏兮兮的前女友
I'm his dusty ex-girlfriend.
另外 我服了他
Also, well played.
他有值得当朋友的潜质
He has friend potential.
不是能帮忙的朋友
Not helpful friend.
是"会吐槽你不该穿啥"的朋友
Just "tell you what not to wear" friend.
时间还早 兰迪应该还没出发...
Well, it's still early, so hopefully Randy hasn't left...
天啊 有免费曲奇
oh, my God, free cookies!
还有黄瓜水
And cucumber water!
还加了浆果
With berries!
我的保姆以前也会在
My nanny used to make me water like this
大轿车送我去读幼儿园前给我做这个
before the town car would take me to preschool.
你家有大轿车吗
You had a town car?
我妈当年就人称城市公交车[大轿车]
My mom was called the town car.
能让四人"做"得舒舒服服
She sat four comfortably.
真不敢相信我得跟平民一起坐面包车去片场
Can't believe I have to take a van to set with other people.
我演过大片《生死时速》呢
I was in Speed.
你还嗑药
You were on speed.
你还进过勒戒所
And you were in rehab.
然后我帮你重建了事业
And then I rebuilt your career,
所以你现在得坐面包车
and now you have to take a van.
麦克斯 看 是兰迪
Max, look! It's Randy.
还有那个反向抵押贷款广告的人
And that guy from the reverse mortgage commercials.
天啊
Ugh! Oh, God!
不能让他看到如此肮脏的我
He can't see me all gross like this.
我还以为你的肮脏
I thought your grossness is
正是他喜欢你的点之一
one of the things he likes about you.
情况有点复杂 他喜欢的是把我从干净变脏
Mm, it's complicated. He likes me to start out clean.
我越来越熟悉
I am getting really good
在公共厕所洗澡的这门技术了
at bathing in public restrooms.
我希望这种日子赶紧到头
And I want it to end!
你的流浪汉技能还没出事
Well, your hobo skills are not complete.
你还得多练习在巷子里撒尿的技术
You need to practice peeing in an alley.
你到现在都还会溅到鞋子上
You're still splashing on your shoes.
走吧 我们去找兰迪
Now come on. Let's go find Randy.
去问问那个柜台小哥
Fine. Let's go ask that concierge
知不知道他去哪里
if he knows where it is.
还记得我们吗
Hey, remember us?
之前的两坨行走尘土团
The dust bunnies from before?
我知道你们是谁
I know who you are.
我一直拿着蒸汽吸尘器在你们后面清理呢
I've been following you two around with a wet vac.
你态度有点不太好啊
Bit of an attitude from someone who's got
你自己还是个头上长一对大角的人呢
two giant horns coming out of his head.
发骚[有角]这事被你提升到了新境界
You're bringing horny to a whole new level.
你能告诉我们电影片场在哪吗
Can you please tell us where the movie set is?
当然啦 没问题 妥妥儿的
Oh, of course. Absolutely. No problem.
先出大堂 左转到主街 然后往右转
Just go out the lobby, make a left on Main, then a right
去到"下辈子都不可能告诉你在哪街"
on There's No Way In Hell I'm Telling You That Street.
你再说一遍是左转还是右转去
Uh, was that a left or a right
"下辈子都不可能告诉你在哪街"
on No Way In Hell I'm Telling You That Street?
听我说 我朋友大老远跑来
Look. My friend came all the way here
想给她男朋友个惊喜
to surprise her boyfriend.
如果是你被人阻止
How would you feel if someone stopped you
跟你男友见面 你会有何感受
from seeing your boyfriend?
不好意思 什么男朋友
Excuse me? Boyfriend?
我可不是基佬
I'm not gay.
这里可是爷们的德州 不是位于
This is Texas, not the Flaming Saddles Saloon
纽约第9大道与52街交叉口的燃烧马鞍同志酒吧
on 9th Avenue and 52nd Street in New York City.
那个你绝对没去过的地方对吧
Where you've definitely never been.
请你们离开我这大厅了好吗
Please just leave my lobby, all right?
这里已经有够多想应征
There's enough sad wannabes around here
临时演员的可悲人士了
with the extras casting...
说到这个
which reminds me
我也得去临演试镜了
I need to get to extras casting.
我们不需要靠他 麦克斯 我有个好主意
We don't need him, Max. I have a great idea.
我们当兰迪电影里的临演就行啦
We'll get cast as extras in Randy's movie.
这样你就能看到他
That way you can see him,
而各地的观众就能看到我
and audiences everywhere can see me.
卡洛琳 这招太绝了
Ah, Caroline, that's genius!
我们等待的期间 我得打给阿憨
While we're waiting, I'll call Han
看看我们甜品酒吧的进度如何
to check on the dessert bar's progress.
我有演艺事业还拥有一家甜品酒吧
Wow. I have an acting career and I own a dessert bar.
再想想 就刚刚
And to think just moments ago
我还在从洗手台泼水洗我私处呢
I was tossing water from a sink to my privates.
如果你没做过爱 还能称呼那为妓女澡吗
Can you call it a whore's bath if you never have sex?
你能请他们小点声吗
Can you please tell them to keep it down?
你说个"不行"就够了啊
A simple "no" would've done.
不需要羞辱我的毛衣吧
You don't have to insult my sweater!
你好啊 麦克斯
And hello, Max.
对面施工传来的"啪啪啪"
There's more banging going on in there
比第一季的《情事》里还多
than season one of The Affair.
真的很破坏我店里的高档用餐环境氛围
It's really ruining the fine dining ambiance in here.
你再说一次 医生
What's that, doc?
是在我蛋蛋上还是在蛋蛋附近而已
Is it on my testicle or just near it?
搞毛啊
Come on!
他们还吵醒了芭芭拉
And now they woke up Barbara.
而且我没带艾米·亚当斯最新的电影光盘
And I don't have the DVD of Amy Adams' last movie
来哄芭芭拉睡着
to put her back to sleep.
骆驼被这最后一根稻草压死 我要过去了
That's the last straw. I'm going over there.
我受不了婴儿哭的声音
I can't stand the sound of a crying baby.
所以我要再等几年才要个孩子
That's why I'm waiting a couple years to have my own.
奥列格
Hey! Oleg.
拜托 你闺女刚被对面的噪音给吵醒了
Come on. Your daughter just got woken up with that heavy noise.
你难道不该过去处理一下吗
You should be going over there.
我正忙着做这个
Uh, I'm kind of in the middle of taking
"你是哪个《老友记》角色"的小测试呢
a "Which Friends character are you?" quiz.
罗斯吗
Ross?
或许你该多做点爷们的事
Well, maybe you should be doing some more manly things
这样芭芭拉看到你的照片时
so that when Barbara sees your picture,
才不会叫"妈妈"
she doesn't say "Mama."
她居然叫我妈妈吗
She calls me Mama?
我现在就过去
I'm going over there.
我才不是妈妈 我是大爹爹斯基
I'm not Mama. I'm Dadushki!
你应该是大傻逼才对
You're being a da-douche-ski.
詹姆士 推挤 基恩 轻轻地
James jostled Gene gently.
詹姆士 推挤 基恩...
James jostled Gene...
谁来帮忙一下啊 我的机器人好像坏了
Somebody help. I think my robot's broken.
麦克斯 这是演员的暖身运动
It's an acting exercise, Max.
有助于拉伸口部肌肉
It stretches out the mouth.
你的大牙就够拉伸你的嘴了吧
Uh, I think all those teeth do the trick.
人家只是准备充分
I just want to be prepared.
也许我来这趟不只是为了陪你
I mean, maybe I'm not just on this journey for you.
或许这也是我被发掘成为女演员的旅程
Maybe I'm supposed to be discovered as an actress.
可能我终于能当一回主角
Maybe something's finally about me.
你所有事情都要永远硬当主角好吗
Everything is always about you.
你把圣诞节称为"卡洛琳得礼物日"
You call Christmas "The Day Caroline Gets Presents."
我们来试镜
And we're only auditioning
是为了让我在片场见到兰迪
so I can get to the set to see Randy.
不是为了你的演艺事业
Not for your acting career.
另外 你才没有什么演艺事业
Also, you don't have an acting career.
你不用练习一下
Well, shouldn't you be practicing
你见到兰迪时要说的话吗
what you're gonna say to Randy?
你原来的"骑上金箍棒"大计
I mean, your original plan to "jump dem bones"
在电影片场可能不太好使
might not fly on a movie set.
我有准备台词好吗
Hey! I got words.
我本来是计划说类似...
I was thinking something along the lines of,
"屎兄 泥嚎啊"
"Howdy, Dude-y."
你懂的 在德州说话要用德州腔
You know, 'cause we're in Texas
而且他这么拉黑我的确是挺屎的
and he was kind of a doody for blocking me.
临演们 这是一部僵尸片
Okay, extras, since this is a zombie movie,
你们得演僵尸给我看
I'm gonna need to see you act like zombies.
但请别碰到我 我全身都是敏感带
But don't touch me. My entire body's an erogenous zone.
僵尸 我没准备好演这个啊
Zombies? I didn't prepare for that.
你也没准备过当一个禁欲的穷人啊
You also didn't prepare for being a celibate poor person,
但你现在还不是当到飞起
but you're knocking that out of the park.
不好意思 先生
Excuse me, sir...
如果这是你的真名的话
if that is your real name.
我们是隔壁餐厅的人
We're from the diner next door,
你最好小声一点
and you need to keep the noise down.
有个小婴儿
It woke up a baby
以及住在二号卡座的人都被你吵醒了
and the man who lives in booth two.
抱歉吵到你们了啊
Sorry for the loud noise.
毕竟要说纽约最出名的事
If there's one thing New York's known for,
就是"安静施工"了吧
it's quiet construction.
听好了 你可能觉得
Listen. You may think you're
自己穿个背心就是啥权威人物之类的
some sort of authority figure with that tank top,
但你并不是
but you're not.
你就是一条"炒鱿鱼"
What you are is fired.
有人帮我录这段给芭芭拉宝宝了吗
Was anyone recording that for baby Barbara?
一瞬间就一发不可收拾了啊
Well, that escalated rather quickly.
请带着你超好看的背心
Take your gorgeous tank top
滚出这里好吗
and get the hell out of here.
行 我不需要受此屈辱
Fine. I don't need this.
我的舞蹈公司刚获得大药厂的拨款呢
My dance company got a grant from Pfizer.
-叩叩叩 -谁在敲
- Knock, knock. - Who's there?
反正没有门能被敲
Not a door.
姑娘们要是回来
The girls are gonna kill me
发现甜品酒吧还没重建完毕 不得杀了我啊
if they get back and the dessert bar isn't finished.
奥列格可以做啊
Well, Oleg will do it.
毕竟他能搞定一切
He says he can nail anything.
我说的是"搞"定新泽西的骚货们
I was talking about Jersey skanks,
但行吧 我试试搞定这个
but sure, I'll give it a try.
录取
You're in.
去尸体临演旁边等
Go wait next to the corpse extras.
下一个
Next.
你好 我叫卡洛琳·钱宁
Hi. My name is Caroline Channing,
我要带来一曲"汉密尔顿"
and I will be singing "Hamilton"
来自同名的音乐剧
from the musical of the same name.
嘴下留人
Hold off on that.
我还没打算要自杀
I'm not quite ready to kill myself.
你确定没有任何非僵尸的角色吗
Are you sure you don't have any non-zombie parts?
比如拉拉队长之类的
Maybe a cheerleader?
或者一个失去万贯家财
Or a socialite who lost all her money
但没失去容貌与向上之心的名媛
but not her looks or her will to succeed?
但她失去了所有人对她的兴趣
But she has lost everyone's interest.
行吧
Uh, fine.
我要演僵尸啦
Here we go with a zombie.
我来啦 我是僵尸
Here I come! I'm a zombie!
天啊 我想回去帮连锁餐厅广告征人了
God, I want to go back to casting commercials for Applebee's.
演员只需要是微胖的白人
You just have to be white and a little fat.
我也可以演...
Or I can do...
这不是僵尸 连屁都不是
Not a zombie. Not anything.
那些汽水是可以免费拿的吗
Hey, are those sodas up for grabs?
是的
Yeah.
还有沙士
Oh-ho! Root beer!
那才是僵尸啊
Now, that's a zombie!
走路姿势跟叫声太棒了 你被录取了
Amazing walk and moan. You're hired.
什么
What?
可是她不是演员啊
But she's not an actor.
她连假装我的笑话好笑都演不出来
She can't even pretend to laugh at my jokes.
你觉得刚才的话好笑吗
You thought that was funny?
没有啊 骗过你了吧
No! Boo.
坏消息 邦邦 我今天不能出镜了
Bad news, Bon Bon: I can't be in your movie today.
卡洛斯不愿意替我前台的班
Carlos won't work my shift at the desk.
我们分...
We broke...
我们吵架了
we had a fight.
看来角色是你的啦
Looks like you got the part.
我手边没人了 恭喜你啊
Congratulations on me running out of people.
好了 大家上面包车
All right, everyone on the van.
得带你们到片场以及画妆
We got to get you to set and makeup.
等等 邦妮 我应该是走
Oh, wait, Bonnie. Am I going with,
"我来啦 我是僵尸"
"Here I come. I'm a zombie."
还是...
or ...?
两种都很好啊
They're both good.
为什么你就能演性感僵尸
Why do you get to be a hot zombie?
而我看起来像死掉的大卫·斯佩德
I look like dead David Spade.
所以就是大卫·斯佩德本人
So, David Spade?
而且我脖子上还有这个很恶心的斧头伤口
And I have this gross axe wound in my neck.
我还以为那是第二张嘴呢
Oh, I thought that was a second mouth.
我本来还担心那嘴会开始说起
I was worried it was gonna start telling stories
自己当年多有钱的故事
about how rich it used to be.
我已经构思好我的僵尸背景故事了
I've been working on my zombie's backstory.
她是一位名叫吉尔的老师
She's a teacher named Jill
沉迷于网络赌博
with an online gambling addiction
喜欢女人 却从未采取任何行动
and an interest in women she's never acted on.
作为你的律师 你能不能别再管我要
So, as your lawyer, can you please stop asking me
醉酒驾照了
for a drunk driver's license?
根本没这玩意
It's not a real thing.
可卡因许可证也不存在
Neither is a cocaine permit.
天啊 是兰迪 快藏起来
Oh, my God, it's Randy. Hide! Hide!
藏 就像吉尔把邻居莎拉的好感
Hide? Like Jill is doing with her feelings
藏起来那样吗
for her neighbor Sarah?
你能和我对下台词吗
Will you run lines with me?
当然
Sure.
你要从这句开始吗 "你可以夺走我的大脑
You want to take it from, "You can take my brains,
但你不能夺走我的自由"
but you can't take my freedom"?
麦克斯 我们千里迢迢来到这
Max, we came all this way.
你不能一直这样躲着他呀
You can't just avoid him forever.
他又不是视频网站的原创剧
He's not a Hulu original.
快去告诉他你想怎么样
Just go tell him what you want.
话说你到底想怎么样
And what do you want?
你打算搬来洛杉矶吗
Are you planning on moving to LA?
因为姐一旦在演艺圈走红
Because when this acting thing takes off,
他们也会想我搬去那里
they'll want me to live there, too.
"他们"是谁
Who's "they"?
纽约的所有民众们吗
Is "they" all of New York?
喂 把大脑放下
Oi! Drop the brains,
你个僵尸渣渣
you zombie scum!
剧本上面写的是"发音轻快"
Yeah, the script says "brightly,"
不是"发音英式"
not "British."
我不能搬去洛杉矶
I mean, I can't move to LA.
我们这么辛苦才有了甜品酒吧的今天
We've worked too hard getting the dessert bar to where it is.
异地恋我也很知足了
I can be happy with the long-distance thing.
我是说 起码比没得恋强
I mean, it's better than nothing,
而且省事 不用老刮毛
and I don't have to shave as much.
没有一样是正儿八经的理由
Well, none of that's A-material,
不过却是你的真实想法
but it's how you feel,
趁他没走 赶紧过去告诉他吧
so just go tell him before he goes off again.
我的断臂在推你呢
I'm pushing you with my stub.
好啦好啦 去就去
All right. All right. I'm going.
为了确保他能认出我
Just to make sure he recognizes me.
你们在这啊 你们俩
Here you are. You two wander off
比我继子的左眼珠子还爱乱跑
more than my stepson's left eye.
你们要迟到了
You're late for your scene.
我得去找刚才离开那个男的 我需要两分钟
Um, I just need two minutes with that guy who just left,
和一个保险套 如果你有的话
and a condom if you have one on you.
你把我当啥人了 调音师那种人吗
What do I look like? The sound guy?
我需要你把裙子拉链拉上
Uh, and I'm gonna need you to zip that dress up.
这电影是家长辅导级
This movie's PG.
好的 我马上拉上
All right, I'll zip up.
看来你们不想拍续集了
Guess you guys don't want a sequel.
好了 那扇门就像把它装上去的那男人一样
There. The door, much like the man who put it up,
好到"屌"炸天
is well hung.
你有没有试过做一件事
Have you ever done anything
不提及自己的老二尺寸的吗
without bringing up your penis size?
有啊 考驾照的时候
Sure. My driver's test.
等等 还真没有
Oh, wait. No.
阿憨 给你提个醒
Han, hey, just a heads up.
老天 现在没有一个人
Man, there's literally no one
在你的餐厅是真正干活的
working in your diner right now.
那不是稀松平常的事吗
And that's unusual how?
既然我不用上班 我要去休息
Well, since I don't have to be at work, I am going on a break,
也就是我要去抽大麻
which means smoking a J
然后去我车上的后备箱小睡一会儿
and taking a nap in the trunk of my car.
他根本没有车好吗
He doesn't even have a car.
怎么样
How about that?
厄尔有超能力
Earl has superpowers.
他拥有的唯一超能力是
The only superpowers he has
至今还活着
is that he's still alive.
到底怎么回事
Hey, what's going on here?
好吧 不用再掩饰了
Fine. The jig is up.
我连门都装不好
I can't hang a door.
苏菲 我的女儿可以把我当成娘儿们
Sophie, my daughter may think I'm a mama,
但我不希望她认为我是骗子
but I don't want her to think I'm a liar.
一瞬间就从小事上升到狗血电视剧的程度了
This went from zero to Lifetime pretty quickly.
我先闪了
I'm out.
奥列格
Oh, Oleg,
别这样 那些都不重要
come on... it doesn't matter
就算你动手能力差 不能保护我们
that you can't build anything or protect us
或是...不像爷们
or... or... or be a man.
最重要的是
What's really important
你有多爱芭芭拉
is how much you love Barbara.
但她觉得我是妈妈
But she thinks I'm a mama.
她还认为丹尼·格洛弗是总统呢
Well, she also thinks that Danny Glover is the president.
大爹爹斯基
Dadushki!
天啊 奥列格 你听见了吗
Oh, my gosh, Oleg, did you hear that?
听见了 你刚说完
Yeah. You just said it.
不不不 那是芭芭拉说的
No. No, no, no. It was Barbara.
芭芭拉刚叫你爹爹
Barbara just called you Dadushki.
是吗
She did?
爸爸
Papa.
"爸爸"是什么鬼啊
"Papa"? What the hell is that?
她不是很聪明
Eh, she's not very bright.
但谢天谢地 她超喜欢她两位妈妈哟
But thank God she's pretty like her mamas.
我的伤口[阴道]好痒啊
Ugh, my gash is itchy.
你应该去看个医生之类的
You should see someone about that.
这是我有史以来上过
This is one of the least comfortable harnesses
最不舒服的吊具
I've ever hung from.
从好的方面看 它包住了我的"三垒"
On the upside, it's currently rounding third base.
羡慕嫉妒恨
Jealous!
里奇 你是怎么来这里的
Oh, Richie! How did you get here?
我以为你要工作呢
I thought you had to work.
不是说演戏不算工作
Not that acting isn't work.
不信问问我的悲剧演员同事 娜塔莉·波特曼
Just ask my fellow thespian, Natalie Portman.
你穿上这衣服就一整个悲剧
You look like a thespian in that shirt.
说来好笑 我其实是坐
Funny story: I actually got here
"关你屁事"快线过来的
on the None of Your Beeswax Express.
他又玩这个哏了
He did it again.
事实证明 怎么玩都不会腻
Turns out it doesn't get old.
好了 僵尸们 还有三分钟开拍
Okay, zombies. Three minutes till we shoot.
让我见识一下你们的蠕动和呻吟
Let me see you wriggle and moan.
邦妮 我呻吟是因为
Bonnie, am I moaning because I am horrified
我对变成僵尸感到恐惧
at what I've become?
还是因为我被挂在肉钩上 所以痛苦地呻吟
Or because I'm in pain from hanging on this meat hook?
她肯定是去问导演了
She must be going to ask the director.
兰迪来了 我看起来怎么样
Here comes Randy. How do I look?
像一坨烂肉
Like a piece of meat.
就当你是赞美了
I'll take it.
你上一场戏太滑稽了
You were hilarious in that last scene.
我觉得大家一定很开心他们没有请艾迪·墨菲
I think everybody's really happy they didn't get Eddie Murphy.
艾迪·墨菲
Eddie Murphy?
我当时就好奇 为什么我吃饭时非得演我全家人
I was wondering why I had to play my whole family at dinner.
这是喜剧片吗
This is a comedy?
幸好我是全能型演技派
Well, it's a good thing I'm so versatile.
我可以变身笨拙搞笑版吉尔
I think I'll make Jill clumsy.
他们去哪儿了
Ugh! Where'd they go?
冥想让我改头换面
Yeah, meditation has totally changed me.
我不再易怒
I'm not as angry.
不准看我
Hey! Don't look at me!
是啊 你看起来平静多了
Yeah, you do seem calmer.
真好奇他们为什么要求你的律师必须陪你拍戏
I wonder why they demanded your lawyer be on set.
兄弟 等我们回洛城
Dude, when we get back to LA,
我帮你介绍个妹子
there's someone I want to set you up with.
我得听听这事 快推我
Oh... I need to hear this. Push me.
她是个辣妹 可我现在不跟
She's hot. But I'm just not dating anyone
开混合动力车的妹子约会
who drives a Prius right now.
我不知道
I don't know.
我现在处境奇怪
I'm in a weird place right now,
我不是说身处德州这地方
and I don't just mean Texas.
你不会还在跟纽约那妹子约会吧
You're not still seeing that girl in New York, are you?
纽约哪个妹子
What girl in New York?
我啊
Me!
你的脑子是被吃了吗
Did your brain get eaten already,
还是吉尔就是个蠢货
or is Jill just an idiot?
吉尔只是生活压力太大
She is just overwhelmed.
她有三个不满五岁的孩子
She has three kids under the age of five
车子还有问题
and car trouble.
我们分手了
We broke up.
我们总是视频
We were Facetiming so much
感觉就像跟自己手机约会
I felt like I was dating my iPhone.
有晚在餐厅吃饭 我和手机分食了一道开胃菜
The other night at dinner, we split an appetizer.
快装死
Play dead!
没错 麦克斯是超级棒
Yeah, Max is incredible,
但我们现在天各一方
but we're just in different places right now.
屁 才不是
No, you're not.
我也希望我能说异地恋
I wish I could say the long distance thing
对我来说足够了
was gonna be enough for me,
但其实不然...永远都不会够
but it wasn't... it wasn't ever gonna be.
恋爱哪有够的时候
It just can't be enough.
就像你喜欢听到关于你发型的赞美
Like you with compliments about your hair.
你喜欢我的发型 对吧
You like it, though, right?
我用尽一切努力想忘掉她
You know, I'm doing everything I can to get over her.
手机屏蔽她的电话 去做心理咨询
Blocked her on my phone, went to therapy,
看了整整13季《实习医生格蕾》
watched all 13 seasons of Grey's Anatomy,
结果意识到我只看了一集的20分钟而已
then realized I'd only watched 20 minutes of one episode.
所以我的发型到底好不好
So, yes or no on my hair?
很赞
It's great.
但我还没准备好去见那个开混合动力车的妹子
But I'm not ready to meet that girl with the Prius just yet.
的确 我很赞成省油的观念
I mean, I'm all for good gas mileage.
但现在还不行
Just not yet.
我懂了 你现在喜欢男人了
I get it. You're gay now.
我倒想呢
I wish!
好了 还有两分钟 各位
All right, two minutes, everybody.
咱们争取一次过 因为这部电影烂死了
Let's do this thing quick, 'cause this movie sucks.
麦克斯 你刚才为什么不说话
Max, why didn't you say something?
那可是你的大好机会
That was your chance.
你也听见他对那个假警长说什么了
Ugh, you heard what he said to that fake sheriff.
他无法满足于异地恋
The long distance thing isn't enough for him,
他需要重新开始
and he needs to move on.
我不应该阻止他
It's only fair that I let him.
叫我傻货吧 我是个浪漫主义者
Call me stupid for being a romantic
相信爱能战胜一切
and thinking love could conquer all.
傻货
Stupid!
很遗憾 麦克斯
I'm sorry, Max.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
你想尿尿吗
Do you have to pee?
因为我发现如果你先尿一点在裤子里
Because I find if you go in your pants a little
然后再尿一点 再一点
and then a little and then a little,
就完全不会那么明显
it's not that noticeable.
我是想给你一个拥抱啦
I was gonna give you a hug.
好吧 来抱吧
All right, bring it in.
-你没事吧 -有事
- You okay? - No.
我这段感情彻底没戏了
My relationship is really over,
而且我下面快失去知觉了
and I'm starting to lose feeling in my downstairs.
是啊
Yeah.
很抱歉拽着你跑了大半个国家
Ugh. I'm sorry I dragged you across the country.
不是你拽着我 是我想陪着你
You didn't drag me anywhere. I wanted to be here with you.
我们回家吧 麦克斯
Let's go home, Max.
我会告诉邦妮我们不演了
I'll tell Bonnie we're quitting.
我们就跟媒体说 因精疲力竭而退出
and we'll tell the press it was exhaustion.
不 我们哪儿不去
No. We're not going anywhere yet.
我们好不容易来到这 至少其中一人
We came all this way. At least one of us should
应该得到自己想要的
get what they want.
你一定要演成这部电影
You are gonna be in this movie.
麦克斯
Max!
等我成了巨星后 我不会忘了你
I won't forget about you when I'm big.
虽然我绝对会因此而少联系
I mean, I'll definitely see you less.
什么意思 不要那个金发妞僵尸是吗
What's that? Get rid of the blonde zombie?
上帝有眼
Oh, thank God.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
因为我的呻吟声吗
Was it my "Mow, mow, mow, mow"?
邦妮 等等 我还能创作呢
Bonnie, wait. I... I can also write.
听听这句台词
Check this line out:
"见到你很鸡冻"
"Freezed to meet you."
把我也放下来吧 邦邦 我们俩分不开
Cut me down, Bon Bon. You can't split us up.
相信我 我试过了
Believe me. I've tried.